ALICE : My name is Alice .
I worked for the Umbrella Corporation ,
the largest and most powerful commercial entity in the world .
I was head of security
at a secret high-tech facility called The Hive ,
a giant underground laboratory
developing experimental viral weaponry .
But there was an incident .
The virus escaped and everybody died .
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
Trouble was ... they didn 't stay dead .
The T-virus reanimated their bodies .
[ GROWLING AND SCREAMING ]
But I survived . Myself and one other ,
an environmentalist named Matt .
When we emerged , we were seized by Umbrella scientists .
Matt and I were separated .
CAIN : He 's mutating .
I want him in the Nemesis Program .
Matt !
CAIN : Take her to the Raccoon City facility ...
and assemble the team .
We 're reopening The Hive .
I want to know what went on down there .
ALICE : We thought we had survived the horror .
But we were wrong .
TV ANNOUNCER : You 're watching Raccoon 7 .
And now , the latest weather with Terri Morales .
It 's 6 : 10 in the a.m.
and already the temperature has reached a massive 92 degrees
as this unprecedented heat wave continues .
Clear skies in Raccoon City
and a light breeze coming in from the west .
And as a special bonus just for you ,
we have a pollen count of 0.7 .
And that 's a record low for this time of year . Good news
for all you hay fever and asthma sufferers .
All in all , it looks like
it 's gonna be another beautiful day .
Stay with us .
After the break , we 're gonna look
at some of your favorite holiday hot spots .
[ METAL RUMBLING ]
CAIN [ OVER RADIO ] : Advance team , proceed .
[ EERIE GRUNTING ]
Sir ?
[ FIERCE GROWLING ]
Holy shit !
[ GROWLING ]
[ TEARING , SPLATTERING ]
[ ¶ ]
[ KNOCKING AT DOOR ]
Excuse us , ma 'am . There 's been an incident .
[ DOORBELL CHIMES ]
Excuse us , sir .
There 's been an incident .
How bad is it ?
You have to come with us .
I have to get my daughter .
It 's been taken care of .
What are you doing ?
Look , you don 't understand . She 's already left for school .
[ CHILDREN WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY ]
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : This is U-Gamma 7 . Evacuation complete ,
but we 've just lost contact with Gamma 12 .
[ BREATHING SOFTLY ]
[ LOCK TURNING , KEYS JANGLE ]
[ RADIO STATIC ]
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : Unit 12 calling for immediate backup
at City Hall .
WOMAN [ ON TV ] : Still no explanation
for this wave of unexplained killings
that is sweeping across this city .
[ GUNFIRE ]
[ GROWLING AND SCREAMING ]
A deadly crime spree with no end .
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : Backup . We need backup now !
MAN 2 [ ON RADIO ] : Just like Valentine told us .
WOMAN [ ON RADIO ] : All off-duty law enforcement personnel
are required to report for duty assignments immediately .
[ CHAOTIC SHOUTING , GUNFIRE ]
Hey ! Give us a hand over here ! This guy 's insane !
MAN : It 's Valentine . MAN 2 : Hold your fire .
Valentine ! They 're infected .
Somebody get this ugly bitch off of me !
[ SNARLS ]
I told you , shoot for the head .
Please , somebody get her !
No , no ! Don 't shoot ! Don 't ...
I 'm leaving town . I suggest you do the same .
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : Everyone 's leaving the city .
We 've received reports of Umbrella Corporation
dispatching armed guards and troop carriers .
[ RADIO TRANSMISSION DISTORTS ]
[ SOFT CLATTERING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ HOWLS ]
[ COCKS RIFLE ]
[ SIREN WAILING ]
GUARD [ ON SPEAKER ] : Move in an orderly fashion
to security checkpoints .
MAN : The city is completely contained , sir .
Our troops have sealed all exits .
The only way out is across this bridge .
GUARD [ ON SPEAKER ] : All citizens must pass through medical scanning .
Sir !
You better take a look at this !
GUARD [ ON SPEAKER ] : Family members
must pass through security checkpoints together .
[ SIRENS WAILING , PEOPLE SHOUTING ]
Please proceed in an orderly fashion .
Do not run .
MAN : He 's clean . Let him pass . MAN 2 : Next !
No pushing , please . Keep in line .
MAN : Can we get some reinforcements down here ?
DISPATCHER [ ON RADIO ] : Chopper Delta , new orders .
Proceed directly to Ravens Gate Bridge .
Reinforcements urgently needed .
PILOT [ ON RADIO ] : Copy that , base . On our way .
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLING ]
Ohh !
[ SNARLING ]
[ SENSOR BEEPING ]
Get it .
No ! No ! Get off !
Get away ! No ! Stop ! Stop ! Get off !
[ FEROCIOUS GROWLING , WOMAN SCREAMS ]
No ! No ! Get away !
No ! Get back !
Civilian in trouble . Three o 'clock . Take us down .
PILOT : I can 't . We have our orders .
No ! Get back ! No ! No !
They 're gonna kill her ! Take us down !
She is a civilian . We have our orders .
[ SNARLING AND GROWLING ]
Fuck orders .
Nicholai , tie me off .
Get back ! No !
PILOT : Wait ! Wait !
Now !
Take us down . Down now !
[ GROWLS ]
Hey ! Hey , you okay ?
Step away from the edge . Come over to me .
Everything 's okay .
No , it 's not .
I 've seen what happens to you once you 've been bitten .
We can help you .
There 's no going back .
No !
[ SIRENS WAILING , CROWD CLAMORING ]
[ CLAMORING ]
Move !
Peyton !
[ VALENTINE WHISTLES ]
Peyton ! Valentine !
Hey ! Hey , Valentine ! Move ! Police . Move !
Hey , let her through .
Hey . Glad you 're here . We could use the help .
[ GRUNTS ]
He has a weak heart .
TROOPER : Get away from him ! Everybody stand back .
Ohh ! Ugh ! Daddy !
Get away ! Get her away from him !
PEYTON : It 's okay . Come on , I got you .
Get her away !
Daddy !
It 's okay . I got you .
[ GIRL SCREAMS ]
Aarrgghhh !
Get him off me ! Get him off me !
Move aside ! Get back !
[ SNARLING AND GROWLING , GIRL SCREAMING ]
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
It 's here .
It 's reached the gate .
Why are you still here ?
You should have got out while you had the chance .
These are our people , Jill .
Close them . Sir ?
Seal the gates .
Our men are still out there- - Just do it .
MAN : My God ! Oh , my God , they 're closing the gates !
[ PEOPLE YELLING ]
[ SIREN WAILING ]
[ CLAMORING ]
MAN : Come on !
CAIN : This is a biohazard quarantine area .
Due to risk of infection ,
you cannot be allowed to leave the city .
TERRI : What the fuck is going on here ?
CAIN : All appropriate measures are being taken .
The situation is under control .
Please return to your homes .
TERRI : You won 't get away with this !
[ CLAMORING ]
[ PEOPLE GASPING ]
CAIN : You have five seconds to turn around
and return to the city .
Do it .
Use of live ammunition
has been authorized .
Five .
They can 't shoot people !
Four . They won 't fire .
Three .
Two . Get them back !
Move !
One .
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
PEYTON : Clear out ! Everybody , clear out .
[ VOICES FADE OUT ]
[ SNARLING AND GROWLING ]
[ AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE ]
DISPATCHER [ ON RADIO ] : Kilo and Romeo squads
rendezvous at sector 01 and secure against enemy .
Grenade ! Grenade !
Squads three to seven are in full retreat .
No , sir . Suppression measures have failed .
We can 't contain it .
The infection is spreading
faster than anyone could have anticipated .
Dr. Ashford .
Shouldn 't you be on the chopper ?
I 'm not going .
I was instructed to get you and the other scientists
out of the hot zone .
You 're too important to Umbrella to be put at risk .
I 'm not leaving without my daughter .
I 'm sorry , truly , but the city is sealed .
She may have survived the crash ,
but we couldn 't find her anywhere .
Even if she was still alive ,
I couldn 't let her out , not now .
The risk of infection is too great .
You must understand .
You do what you have to do .
I 'm staying .
There has to be someone left alive .
Come on .
[ GASPS ]
[ MOANS ]
[ RETCHES ]
Matt !
CAIN : Take her to the Raccoon City facility .
I want her quarantined . Close observation .
ASHFORD : Prepare for exposure .
Up the dosage .
Just do it .
Inside .
Let 's get under cover .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
MAN : You have to get out !
This is my place . I 'm hiding here .
It 's big enough for all of us .
Don 't tell me what- -
Okay , just cool it . Put the gun down .
Put the gun down .
And , you , take it easy .
So does the Raccoon City Police Department
have any comment on what those things are ?
What 's that you got there ?
My ... Emmy .
That 's if any of us make it out of here .
[ CREAKING ]
[ METAL CLANGS ]
Are you all right ?
MAN : What are you doing ?
What 's wrong ?
It 's my sister . She 's not well .
Maybe I can help . [ SNARLS ]
No . Out of my way !
[ WOMAN GROWLS ] Just get out !
You 're feeding her ? You 're sick .
[ GROWLING FEROCIOUSLY ]
Just leave us alone .
[ WOMAN SNARLING VICIOUSLY ]
No !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
TERRI : I 'm getting out of here .
PEYTON : Hey !
Hey ! Hey , no !
[ GROWLING AND SCREAMING ]
PEYTON : Hey , help us !
Help !
Get it in there ! Get it in there !
[ LOUD THUMPING AGAINST DOOR ]
[ POUNDING SILENCES ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GASPS ] What the hell was that ?
[ SNARLING ]
There !
Jesus !
TERRI : What the fuck is that thing ?
PEYTON : Hey , what are you doing ? Get back here !
[ MENACING GROWL ]
[ PANTING ]
[ CREATURE SNARLS ]
[ METAL SQUEAKING ]
[ RATTLING ]
[ CRASH ]
[ METAL CLATTERING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ MAN SCREAMS ]
[ DISTANT CLANG ]
[ CREAKING ]
[ FAINT SCRATCHING ]
VALENTINE [ WHISPERING ] : Peyton . Terri .
[ SHRIEKS ]
Peyton ! Shhh !
[ SNARLING ]
I know .
PEYTON : I count three of them .
They got us boxed in .
What are we gonna do ?
Let 's go !
Oh !
Jesus !
We 're gonna need more ammo .
VALENTINE : I 'm out .
[ CREATURE SNARLS ]
[ GUN CLICKING ]
Shit ! I 'm out .
Move !
VALENTINE : Who the fuck are you ?
GTA , motherfucker !
Arggh !
Oh !
Yeah ! Ten points !
[ GUNFIRE IN DISTANCE ]
[ GUN CLICKING ]
Yuri , you okay ?
Uh-huh .
Bite this !
Are you okay ? Yeah .
Yeah .
CARLOS : Pull back ! Pull back !
[ GUNSHOTS , GRUNTING ]
CARLOS : This way .
CARLOS : This is Olivera .
We 've been overrun . Request immediate chopper evac .
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
[ LOW GROWLING ]
We need to find somewhere to stop for a moment .
Uh-uh . I don 't think that 's a good idea .
There might be more of those ... things .
If there were more , we 'd have seen them by now .
So you know what they are ?
They 're bio-weapons
from the Umbrella labs beneath the city .
How come you know so much about Umbrella ?
I used to work for them .
Oh ! Damn it !
Hold it .
What do you think you 're doing ?
He 's wounded . The infection 's spreading .
I 'm fine .
You should take care of him now .
It 'll be more difficult later .
You know that .
No .
If it comes to that ,
I 'll take care of it myself .
As you wish .
It 's nothing personal .
But in an hour , maybe two , you 'll be dead .
And moments later , you 'll become one of them .
You 'll endanger your friends ,
try to kill them , probably succeed .
I 'm sorry .
That 's just the way it is .
[ SHRIEKS ]
Help me !
ALICE : There 's too many of them .
Let 's get out of here . This way .
WOMAN : Sir , T-virus infection has reached critical levels .
CAIN : This presents a perfect opportunity .
Ensure all data streams are recorded .
Activate Nemesis Program now .
Hey ! Here !
Here ! We 're down here !
Come ! Come ! We 're here !
Where are they going ?
They 're landing over there . Let 's get Yuri . Come on !
CARLOS : Come on , Yuri , we 're getting out of here .
NICHOLAI : We 'll get you fixed up . Come .
CARLOS : Hold on , Yuri . We 're almost there .
No .
No ! Don 't leave !
No , we 're down here ! We 're coming !
They dropped something in the hospital . Did you see it ?
Maybe a radio . One that works .
Take Yuri .
Hold on .
NICHOLAI : Hold on , Yuri .
YURI : Nicholai , put me down .
Okay . Rest here .
NICHOLAI : What is this ?
CARLOS : Looks like weapon cases .
We don 't need weapons . We need evacuation !
These weren 't meant for us .
[ NICHOLAI SCREAMS ]
Yuri !
Plenty to go around .
Whoo-hoo !
[ LAUGHS ]
[ MUSIC LEAKS OUT OF HEADPHONES ]
Don 't shoot !
[ MAN LAUGHS ]
I got the power .
Thank you . I owe you one , man .
Shit !
Maybe I was safer outside .
Get them guns out of my damn face .
Motherfucker , please . Look .
My shit is custom .
Shh !
What the fuck 's that ?
Shhhhhit !
You 're going down , you son of a bitch !
[ GROWLS ]
Fuck !
LEADER : Deploy defensive formation . Take him down .
You motherfuckers is crazy .
Look at that big motherfucker , got a rocket launcher !
CAIN : What do we have ?
A dozen armed men . Well organized .
I 'm surprised there 's anyone left alive .
They 're S.T.A.R.S.
Special Tactics and Rescue Squad .
They 're the best .
[ GROWLS ] MAN : Fire !
Back ! Fall back !
Let 's see how good
they really are .
Altering protocols .
[ YELLING ]
[ CONTINUES YELLING ]
[ GUTTURALLY ] S.T.A.R.S.
Oh , shit .
[ HEAVY FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
Respect .
[ GROWLS ]
[ FOOTSTEPS THUDDING ]
VALENTINE : Those were some pretty slick moves back there .
I 'm good ...
but I 'm not that good .
You should be thankful for that .
What do you mean ?
They did something to me .
I barely feel human anymore .
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
We should keep moving ,
before the sound attracts anything .
[ RINGING CEASES ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
Keep moving .
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
Hello ?
ASHFORD : God , I thought you 'd never answer .
Who is this ?
I can get you out of the city .
All four of you .
But first we have to come to an arrangement .
Are you ready to make a deal ?
ALICE : Do we have a choice ?
Not if you want to live beyond tonight , no .
VALENTINE : So his name is Dr. Ashford , and he runs- -
ALICE : Runs the advanced genetics
and viral research division
of the Umbrella Corporation .
What 's he want with us ? His daughter ,
Angela , is trapped within the city .
Umbrella was supposed to evac her , but she didn 't make it .
She 's hiding out in her school .
We find her , he 'll help us escape the perimeter .
No fucking deal .
We find the building with the thickest walls
and strongest doors
and we barricade ourselves in ,
sit tight , wait for help .
There won 't be any help .
According to Ashford ,
Umbrella know they can 't contain the infection .
So at sunrise this morning ,
Raccoon City will be completely sanitized .
What do you mean by " sanitized " ?
A precision tactical nuclear device .
What yield ?
Five kilotons .
[ SCOFFS ]
Fuck me .
[ MUTTERING ] Stupid ...
What does that mean ?
It means that it 'll destroy the infection ...
[ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
... and all evidence of it .
PEYTON : It 's bullshit .
It 's bullshit !
No fucking way would they get away with that !
It would be all over the fucking news !
Cover-up .
Cover-up is already prepared .
A meltdown at the nuclear power plant .
A tragic accident .
Not even Umbrella 's capable of this .
VALENTINE : Not capable ?
Peyton , you were there at the bridge .
You know exactly how far Umbrella will go .
So , what do we do now ? Huh ?
I think we should be out of here by sunrise .
VALENTINE : What if there is no way out of the city
and he 's watching us on these cameras
like this is some kind of sick game ?
[ WHOOSHING ]
VALENTINE : What is it ?
What 's going on ? Wait .
The sunrise ain 't gonna wait .
No .
There 's something down there .
VALENTINE : Where ?
There .
PEYTON : I don 't see anything .
ALICE : Well , that doesn 't alter the fact
that there is ... something down there .
I 'm getting sick of this bullshit !
Peyton !
No !
He 's located another two S.T.A.R.S. members .
Nemesis .
Run .
Just go !
[ GROWLS ]
Primary target is identified .
Gentlemen , this is what we 've been waiting for .
[ ROARS ]
Confirm at 2 : 18 and 27 seconds .
The Nemesis Program is now fully activated .
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GASPING BREATHS ]
[ ENGINE CRANKING ]
[ POUNDING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ CONTINUES CRANKING ENGINE ]
Look , I 'm- - I 'm sorry about your friend .
[ SNIFFS ]
Let 's just get to the school and find this kid .
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
[ GROWLING ]
Peyton !
[ BODY THUDS ]
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
CARLOS : Huh . This bite ,
it won 't stop bleeding .
NICHOLAI : Why didn 't they see us ?
What ?
The chopper .
We were right there in the street
in front of the hospital . How could they not see us ?
They saw us .
What do you mean ?
[ SIGHS ]
We 're assets , Nicholai .
Expendable assets .
And we 've just been expended .
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
Stop !
I 'm not one of those things !
Hey ! Remember me ?
Look , I haven 't been bitten or anything . Look .
Climb aboard .
Lloyd Jefferson Wade .
You can call me L.J. on account of the informal situation .
[ CAR DOORS CLOSE ]
VALENTINE : We 're gonna have to split up to search this place .
Forget it .
Forget it . I 'm not going out there by myself !
I can go with you .
You , take the first floor .
You , take the second .
I 'll take the basement .
I 've never shot a gun before .
There 's nothing to it .
Try to hit them in the head .
[ RUSTLING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
I see you , mother- -
[ GROWLS ] Oh , shit !
So did you get the call as well ?
What ?
You 're here for the girl ?
Oh , yeah , yeah . The girl .
Dr. Ashford didn 't say he made a deal with someone else .
I guess we 're partners .
Shit .
[ METAL CLANGS ] [ SHRIEKS ]
Angela ?
It 's gonna be okay .
There 's no need to be afraid .
We 're gonna take you home .
[ SNARLS ] [ SCREAMS ]
Oh , my God . Oh , my God .
[ GROWLING , TERRI SCREAMING ]
God ! Help me !
[ TERRI SCREAMS ]
Help !
[ TERRI CONTINUES SCREAMING ]
[ DISTANT SCREAM ]
Terri ?
GIRL : You can 't help her .
Not now .
I 've seen what they do .
Are you Angela ?
Yes .
We should hurry before they come back .
Hold this .
VALENTINE : Angela Ashford , huh ?
That 's a pretty grown-up name for a little girl .
I 'm not a little girl .
Besides ...
all my friends call me Angie .
Angie , huh ?
I like that .
ANGELA : Those things are in here .
VALENTINE : It 's okay , honey , they 're slow .
We can run around them .
ANGELA : No , not them .
Them .
Get back .
[ BARKS FEROCIOUSLY ]
Stay .
Thought you might need a hand .
You work for Umbrella ?
Used to .
Till they left us for dead in this place .
Now I consider myself freelance .
Sergeant Nicholai Genovev , at your service .
Come on ! Wait ! Angie !
Save the girl !
I 've got this bitch .
[ SNARLING ]
Oh , shit .
[ SCREAMING ]
VALENTINE : From now on , stay right beside me .
ANGELA : It 's blocked .
What do we do now ?
Wait here .
Eyes ...
Okay ?
[ BARKING ]
[ COUGHS ]
Thank you .
You two know each other ?
She 's infected .
She 's infected on a massive level .
How can you know that ?
Because she is too .
You 're infected ?
When were you gonna tell us that ?
Let me see . No .
You know I 'm not gonna hurt you .
Let me see .
ALICE : It 's the antivirus , the cure to the T-virus .
There 's a cure ?
How did you get this ?
My daddy .
My daddy made it for me .
He 's sick .
And someday , I 'll get sick too .
He just wanted to stop that .
When I was little ...
I had to walk on crutches .
They said I 'd never get better , just worse .
He found a way to make me stronger .
ALICE : The T-virus .
[ MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
ANGELA : Then they took the invention away from him .
ASHFORD : Get out of my house !
He 's not a bad man .
He didn 't mean for any of this .
It 's okay .
[ BANG ]
Don 't shoot , don 't shoot .
He 's cool .
He made a deal with Dr. Doom , same as you .
How many of you guys are there ?
What do you mean ?
Nicholai .
[ COUGHS AND SPLUTTERS ]
When were you bitten ?
Three hours ago . What the- - ?
It 's your lucky day .
You should have told me you got bit , motherfucker .
I 'm hanging with you and shit .
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
ASHFORD : Let me speak to my daughter .
First , you tell us how we 're getting out .
There 's a helicopter already being prepped .
It takes off in 47 minutes .
It 'll be the last transport to leave Raccoon City
before they detonate the missile .
I take it this helicopter isn 't laid out especially for us .
No . It has another purpose , but it 'll be lightly guarded .
Where is the evac site ?
May I speak to my daughter now ?
Daddy ?
Hey , sweetheart .
Are you all right ?
When can I see you ?
Soon .
These people will bring you to see me .
I 'll see you very soon .
Put the lady back on .
ALICE : Where do we have to go ?
The helicopter will be at City Hall .
I suggest you make haste .
Computers . So unreliable .
Just like people .
You really thought I didn 't know ?
So , what are you injecting me with ?
The antivirus .
The T-virus reanimates dead cells .
Basically , bringing the dead to life .
Or in a living human ,
it can cause uncontrollable mutation .
Or it can help her walk again ,
if the virus is kept in check with this .
Angie 's infected ?
ALICE : Yes .
The cellular growth is enough to regenerate her ,
but not enough to cause further mutation .
And they infected you with the T-virus as well ?
Yeah .
[ GROANS ]
But don 't worry , I 'm not contagious .
Here .
Tape the story .
I 'll see that it gets put to good use .
My name is Alice .
I worked for the Umbrella Corporation ,
the largest and most powerful commercial entity in the world .
I was head of security
at a secret high-tech facility called The Hive ,
a giant underground laboratory
developing experimental viral weaponry .
Let 's go .
Hey !
You missed one .
[ LAUGHS HOARSELY ]
[ COMPUTER BEEPING ]
We have to hurry .
We 're okay . We have time .
No ! We have to hurry .
[ FOOTSTEPS THUDDING ]
Holy shit ! We stealing his ride .
Take off .
I said take off !
What 's the rush ?
We 've been expecting you .
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : Perimeter secure .
MAN 2 : All sectors locked down .
Angie !
Daddy .
Hey . I knew you wouldn 't leave me .
No , no , never , never .
Discard primary weaponry .
The two of you showed such promise ,
but we had to see you in action .
And most impressive you 've been .
You 're like brother and sister .
Heightened speed , strength , agility ,
the same killer instincts .
Parallel strands of research .
And now ... Now we discover
which is superior .
Fight him .
No .
Fight him or they die .
What makes you think I care ?
Daddy ! Daddy , no !
Son of a- -
No !
He was a valuable asset to the corporation .
I don 't even care about these people .
[ GRUNTS ANGRILY ]
[ ANGELA SOBS ]
Begin .
[ ROARS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLS ]
CAIN : He 's mutating .
I want him in the Nemesis Program .
Matt !
[ WHIMPERS ]
SCIENTIST : Cellular structure breaking down .
FEMALE SCIENTIST : T-virus is manifesting itself
in a genetic mutation .
We 're seeing similar cellular regeneration .
[ SOBBING ]
I 'm sorry .
Oh , Matt , I 'm- - I 'm so sorry .
[ WHIMPERS ]
Finish him .
I said , finish him .
No .
Don 't you understand how important you are to me ?
That creature is one thing , but you ...
Somehow you bonded with the T-virus on a cellular level .
You adapted it , changed it .
You became ... magnificent .
I became a freak .
No , you 're not mutation . You 're evolution .
With my help ,
just imagine what you can achieve .
What about him ?
Evolution has its dead ends .
Now , finish this .
Put him out of his misery .
And come with me .
No .
You 're such a disappointment to me .
All that strength , but no will to use it .
What a waste .
[ SNARLS ]
[ MATT GROWLS ]
Prepare for takeoff .
Sanitation of Raccoon City to commence on my mark .
Kill her .
[ GROWLS ]
What are you doing ?
Get us airborne .
This is Cain . Priority overload .
Initiate launch proceedings .
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : Detonation set at T-minus 5 minutes .
Angie , get down !
Why haven 't we taken off ?
Because I usually drive a Cadillac .
[ GROWLS ]
[ GASPS ]
PILOT [ ON SPEAKERS ] : Surrender , or we open fire .
Drop it .
ANGELA : Alice !
PILOT [ ON SPEAKERS ] : Drop your weapon and surrender .
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ GROWLING ]
Let 's get this thing in the air !
You have to get up .
Matt ...
Come on , we have to go .
We have to go , come on .
Come on .
[ GROWLING ]
Get up !
CAIN : If you expect me to beg ,
I will not .
Wait !
[ GRUNTS ]
Killing me won 't put things right .
No !
But it 's a start .
Ah !
[ GUN CLICKS ]
[ CAIN SCREAMING ]
Are you going to be all right ?
Hang on to something !
[ GASPS ]
CARLOS : We 're going down !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : U-Gamma 9 to base . Confirmation .
We 've located the crash site .
Fetch the medical team .
What about the others ?
MAN : No other bodies found , sir .
FEMALE REPORTER : We have unconfirmed reports
of disaster at Raccoon City .
These shocking images just in .
A mysterious plague or viral outbreak
seems to have run rampant- -
... implicating the Umbrella Corporation
in the death of innocent citizens .
MALE REPORTER : This tape , apparently the work
of former Raccoon 7 anchorwoman Terri Morales .
New evidence now , which discreditsearlier reports- -
This is nothing more than a sick joke .
Fake videotape now totally discredited .
Nothing more than an elaborate hoax .
Playing on the very real tragedy
which overwhelmed Raccoon City earlier this week .
MALE REPORTER 2 : Apparently , the reactor at the nuclear power station
went critical in the early hours .
MALE REPORTER 3 : Making this the worst atomic energy disaster
since the Russian Chernobyl incident in 1986 .
The state governor has personally extended his thanks
to the Umbrella Corporation for their swift actions .
FEMALE REPORTER 3 : The perpetrators of the hoax ,
Jill Valentine and Carlos Olivera ,
now being sought for questioning by the police .
ANGELA [ ECHOING WHISPER ] : Alice .
Alice .
Wake up .
Can you hear me ?
Do you understand what I 'm saying ?
Good .
Begin the purging process .
[ COMPUTER BEEPING ]
WOMAN : Her recovery 's remarkable .
And her powers , both physical and mental ,
are developing at a geometric rate .
[ GASPING ]
Wh- - Wh- -
Wh- -
[ COUGHS ]
Where are you ?
Where ?
You 're safe .
Come on .
That 's it .
There we are .
Do you know what that is ?
It 's a pen .
See ?
You try .
That 's it .
P- - Pen .
P- -
Look at me .
Can you remember anything ?
Hmm ?
You remember your name ?
My name ?
My name ...
[ COUGHS ]
I want her under 24-hour observation .
I want a complete set of blood work ,
chemical and electrolyte analysis by the end of the day .
My name ...
My name ... Sir ?
Advanced reflex testing is also a priority .
My name ...
I want her electrical impulses monitored and her- -
Sir ?
Sir !
What is it ?
My name ...
is Alice .
[ LAUGHS ]
And I remember everything .
Oh ! Uggh !
[ SCREAMING ]
This is central . Request immediate backup .
Maximum response .
[ ALARM SOUNDING ]
[ GUARD GROANS ]
Ahh !
[ GUNS COCKING ]
Thank you , gentlemen .
We 'll take over from here .
On whose authority ? Classified .
Level six authorization .
Sorry , sir .
[ GLASS TINKLING ]
[ PHONE RINGING ]
Let them go .
CARLOS : Good to have you back .
Are you all right ?
Program Alice activated .
What did they do to you ?
[ KILLSWITCH ENGAGE 'S " THE END OF HEARTACHE " PLAYING ]
¶ Seek me
¶ Call me
¶ I 'll be waiting ¶
¶ Seek me
¶ Call me
¶ I 'll be waiting ¶
¶ This distance
¶ This dissolution
¶ I cling to memories
¶ While falling
¶ Sleep brings release
¶ And the hope of a new day
¶ Waking the misery
¶ Of being without you
¶ Surrender
¶ I give in
¶ Seek me
¶ For comfort
¶ Call me For so- - ¶
WOMAN : This is a product of the Umbrella Corporation .
Our business is life itself .
Some side effects may occur .
[ " THE END OF HEARTACHE " RESUMES ]
¶ Seek me
¶ Completion
¶ Call me
¶ I 'll be waiting ¶
¶ For the end
¶ Of my broken heart
¶ You know me
¶ You know me all too well
¶ My only desire
¶ To bridge our division
¶ In sorrow
¶ I speak your name
¶ And my voice mirrors
¶ Mirrors my torment
¶ Seek me
¶ For comfort
¶ Call me
¶ For solace
¶ I 'll be waiting ¶
¶ For the end
¶ Of my broken heart
¶ Seek me
¶ Completion
¶ Call me
¶ I 'll be waiting ¶
¶ For the end
¶ Of my broken heart
[ SLIPKNOT 'S " VERMILLION " PLAYING ]
¶ She seems dressed In all the rings ¶
¶ Of past fatalities
¶ So fragile yet so devious
¶ She continues to see it
¶ Climatic hands that press
¶ Her temples and my chest
¶ Enter the night That she came home ¶
¶ Forever
¶ Oh
¶ She 's the only one That makes me sad ¶
¶ She is everything and more
¶ The solemn hypnotic
¶ My dahlia Bathed in possession ¶
¶ She is home to me
¶ I get nervous , perverse
¶ When I see her , it 's worse ¶
¶ But the stress is astounding
¶ It 's now or never ¶
¶ She 's coming home ¶
¶ Forever
¶ Oh
¶ She 's the only one That makes me sad ¶
¶ Hard to say What caught my attention ¶
¶ Vixen crazy Ain 't that attraction ? ¶
¶ Carve my name in my face
¶ To recognize
¶ Such a pheromone cult
¶ To terrorize
¶ I won 't let this Build up inside of me ¶
¶ Yeah